I just wanted to ask you about the
process here with the Dolphins and
getting through the Senior Bowl and the
combine and kind of how it was with the
Dolphins throughout the process of of
getting ready for the draft.
Uh really we did like I feel like it was
a regular process. I had like regular
meeting with them.
Then I came back combine same thing.
Really nothing just too extravagant.
And what would you say is the skill that
kind of separates you or
the skill that is your calling card in
terms of what you do really well? What's
the What's the best part about your
game?
That I I can stretch field. I can go out
there
and play in small spaces in my in my
size.
Well, thanks, man. Welcome to Miami.
Thank you.
Chris?
Hey, what's up, Caleb? Chris Perkins
from the South Florida Sun Sentinel.
Congratulations. Thank you, man. Thank
you.
Hey, tell me about your reaction to
being picked by the Dolphins. Was this a
surprise to you? Did you expect this? Uh
I always a surprise, man, especially
with this draft. So, yeah, for surely.
Did you Did you have much contact with
them pre-draft, a 30 visit? Did you talk
to them at the Senior Bowl, anything
like that? I I had Senior Bowl talk to
them combine, but other than that I
didn't have a 30 or nothing like that.
Okay. All right. Appreciate you.
Congratulations. Thank you.
David?
Hey, Caleb. David Furones here also from
the South Florida Sun Sentinel.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Yeah, what do you think about teaming up
with Jacob Rodriguez after he was a
>> Hey, hey, I told J-Rod hey, I can't wait
to be teammates again.
>> [laughter]
[clears throat]
>> That's awesome, man. What do you think
you can do with with Malik Willis at
quarterback? Man, a a whole lot. I ain't
going to lie to you. Even when he was at
the Titans, I I loved him. So, I I'm I'm
happy I'm I'm paired up with him. We
going to go out there and do it.
Great. Thank you.
Thank you.
Isaiah?
Hey, Caleb. Isaiah Smalls from the Miami
Herald. Congratulations. Again, welcome
to South Florida.
Just looking at your numbers, you really
flourished when you arrived at Texas
Tech. Just what was it about that
program that kind of allowed you to be
your best self?
Uh really just around about all the
coaches for real and them putting me in
great opportunities and showing me how
to go out there and just make sure I'm
making sure I'm I'm staying front
focused. Just going out there making
sure I'm making plays that I make. So,
yeah.
And then just I don't know if you've
gotten a chance to look at the Dolphins
receiver
>> [clears throat]
>> room as of late, but you know, you'll
have a real chance to compete from day
one. Just what do you think about that
opportunity?
Oh, yeah, great opportunity for real.
Even if it wasn't opportunity, I'm going
to go out there and compete compete
regardless. So, really I'm I'm
appreciative of the opportunity.
Appreciate you, man.
David?
Hey, Caleb.
Give me an idea of how do you use your
big 6'3 and 1/2 frame, long arms? How do
you like to use that when going up for
for football season?
Uh really like you said, that using my
frame, making sure I go out there and do
what I'm supposed to do for real.
Nothing really extra to it.